<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Deep Tracking</title>
    <link>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Deep Tracking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:52:06 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Universe in the Lab.</title>
      <link>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:52:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/fair/</guid>
      <description>Facility for Antiproton and Ion Research (FAIR) is a future facility being build at GSI Darmstadt. Watch the introduction below.   ![Straw Tube Tracker](/images/trk.gif) ![Straw Tube Tracker](/images/stt.jpg) ![Panda Experiment](/images/panda.jpg) -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proton Annihilation</title>
      <link>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/panda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:52:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/panda/</guid>
      <description>The full dector being built at FAIR adjacent to GSI Helmholtz Center for Heavy Ion Research. Proton ANnihiation at DArmstadt (PANDA) is shown below:
The sub-detector, STT is part of the central tracking system at PANDA. Made from Straw Tubes, gives $4\pi$ coverage.
![Straw Tube Tracker](/images/trk.gif) ![Straw Tube Tracker](/images/stt.jpg) ![Panda Experiment](/images/panda.jpg) -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep.TrkX</title>
      <link>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/deeptrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:52:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/deeptrx/</guid>
      <description>Deep.TrkX (Deep Learning for Tracking) is a project launched at Uppsala University which is mandated to explore deep use of deep learning for event and track reconstruciton in PANDA Experiment (See below). Some of the techniques being used are Dense Network (DNN), Covulutional (CNN)* and Recurrent Networks (RNN).
*Courtesy of asimovinstitute.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compressed Baryonic Matter</title>
      <link>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/cbm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 22:39:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deeptrkx.github.io/project/cbm/</guid>
      <description>The Compressed Baryonic Matter (CBM) experiment will be one of the major scientific pillars of the future Facility for Antiproton and Ion Research (FAIR) in Darmstadt. The goal of the CBM research program is to explore the QCD phase diagram in the region of high baryon densities using high-energy nucleus-nucleus collisions. This includes the study of the equation-of-state of nuclear matter at neutron star core densities, and the search for phase transitions, chiral symmetry restoration, and exotic forms of (strange) QCD matter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>